Oishwaryaa Chhatui

Kolkata, IN | oishwaryaac@gmail.com | (+91) 6289613059 |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/oishwarvaa-chhatui-824894231/ | https://linktr.ee/oishwarvaa

PROFILE

Hi, I am Oishwaryaa Chhatui. I am an experienced Content Specialist with an ongoing Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration specialising in Marketing Management with extensive experience in leadership, communication, and data literacy. My certifications in digital marketing and ongoing web development studies expand my expertise. Fluent in three languages and passionate about music, digital marketing, and web development - I offer a diverse skill set for overall team success.

EDUCATION

• Bachelor's degree in Business Administration | Marketing Management D.Y. Patil International University Online

• Higher Secondary School | 10+2 | Commerce National Institute of Open Schooling

July 2023 to Present

April 2014 to April 2016

SKILLS

- Strategic Leadership (4 years)
- Leadership (5 years)
- Communication skills (10+ years)
- Data Literacy (4 years)
- Adaptability (10+ years)
- Microsoft Office (10+ vears)
- Google Suite (5 years)
- Organisational skills (4 years)
- Administrative experience (4 years)
- Customer service (5 years)

- Team management (4 years)
- OBS (5 years)
- Streamlabs OBS (5 years)
- Zoom (5 years)
- Video editing (5 years)
- Marketing (2 years)
- Customer retention (4 years)
- E-Commerce (1 year)
- Analytics (4 years)
- Customer support (5 years)
- People management (4 years)

- Music Production (5 years)
- Singing (10+ years)
- Songwriting (2 years)
- Cubase (5 years)
- MAGIX Video Editing (2 years)
- Canva (2 years)
- Inshot (2 years)
- Adobe Premiere Rush (2 years)
- Adobe Express (2 years)
- Adobe Creative Cloud (2 years)
- FL Studio (5 years)

WORK EXPERIENCE

1. Digital Examination Representative

London College of Music | London, UK (Remote)

September 2020 to September 2023

- Developed creative designs for print and digital marketing campaigns that increased brand awareness by 20%
- Assisted students in appearing for digital music exams and understanding digital citizenship

2. Music Teacher & Curriculum Developer

Artium Academy | Mumbai, IN (Remote)

 Developed a comprehensive western music curriculum that met all standards and was successfully adopted by the school that improved student performance by 35%

Taught a variety of music styles and genres, including classical, jazz, and popular music

3. Vocal Music Instructor

January 2020 to September 2020

November 2022 to April 2023

DIY (by Kyt) | Bangalore, IN (Remote)

- Taught a variety of music styles and genres, including classical, jazz, and popular music, etc.
- Created an innovative music program that increased student interest in music and participation in performances

ACHIEVEMENTS

• ZEE Bangla Sa Re Ga Ma Pa 2014 | TOP 13 Contestant

October 2014

• And TV The Voice India 2015 | TOP 20 Contestant

October 2015

CERTIFICATIONS

• Foundations of Digital Marketing and E-commerce

Google Career Certificates
Coursera

July, 2023

Verify at https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/FPZ6VCKFPNTS

Attract and Engage Customers with Digital Marketing

Google Career Certificates Coursera

Sep, 2023

Verify at https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/AK6MMTVZTCEN

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy Certificates

By Dr. Angela Yu from London App Brewery

Currently pursuing

• Google Digital Marketing & E-commerce Professional Certificate

Google Career Certificates
Coursera

Currently pursuing

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent

Hindi

Fluent

Bengali (Bangla)

Fluent

INTERESTS

- Singing
- Music Production
- Video Editing
- Audio Editing
- Graphics Design
- Digital Marketing
- Web Development

CREATIVE PORTFOLIO & SOCIAL MEDIA

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/oishwaryaa-chhatui-824894231/
- Linktree: https://linktr.ee/oishwaryaa
 (Contains complete creative portfolio)
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/singer.oishwaryaa
- Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/wishyouwell.inhell/

CONTACT DETAILS

Primary phone: (+91) 62896 13059
Secondary phone: (+91) 98366 75052

• Primary email: oishwaryaac@gmail.com

• Secondary email: oishwaryaa.chhatui@gmail.com